[{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678685559,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":10152,"timeElapsed":33940},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678693240,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":7679,"timeElapsed":41622},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678698595,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":5352,"timeElapsed":46977},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678705149,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":6551,"timeElapsed":53531},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678709060,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3910,"timeElapsed":57442},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678713409,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":4346,"timeElapsed":61791},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678716550,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3139,"timeElapsed":64932},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678720356,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3804,"timeElapsed":68738},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678724118,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3760,"timeElapsed":72500},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678732685,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":6787,"timeElapsed":81066},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678736272,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3585,"timeElapsed":84654},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678739658,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":3384,"timeElapsed":88040},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678741897,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2236,"timeElapsed":90279},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678744278,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":2380,"timeElapsed":92660},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678749423,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5142,"timeElapsed":97804},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678754358,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":4934,"timeElapsed":102740},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678757859,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":3499,"timeElapsed":106241},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678760814,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":2953,"timeElapsed":109196},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678778866,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":16553,"timeElapsed":127248},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678782051,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3183,"timeElapsed":130433},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678785709,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3655,"timeElapsed":134090},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678789401,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3691,"timeElapsed":137783},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678792280,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2876,"timeElapsed":140661},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678796270,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":3988,"timeElapsed":144652},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678800145,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":3874,"timeElapsed":148527},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678804162,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":4016,"timeElapsed":152544},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678807312,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3148,"timeElapsed":155694},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678823561,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":15144,"timeElapsed":171942},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678827025,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":3463,"timeElapsed":175407},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678829388,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":2361,"timeElapsed":177770},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678831479,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2089,"timeElapsed":179861},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678834708,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":3227,"timeElapsed":183090},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678839774,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":5063,"timeElapsed":188156},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678845689,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":5913,"timeElapsed":194071},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678849267,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":3577,"timeElapsed":197649},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678852172,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":2903,"timeElapsed":200554},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678861972,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3928,"timeElapsed":210354},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678865131,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3157,"timeElapsed":213513},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678868412,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3279,"timeElapsed":216794},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678871212,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2798,"timeElapsed":219594},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678874814,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3600,"timeElapsed":223196},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678877257,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2443,"timeElapsed":225639},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678880110,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2852,"timeElapsed":228492},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678889700,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":9588,"timeElapsed":238082},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678896586,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":6885,"timeElapsed":244968},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678902650,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":4618,"timeElapsed":251032},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678906849,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":4197,"timeElapsed":255231},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678910132,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":3281,"timeElapsed":258513},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678913719,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":3585,"timeElapsed":262101},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678919765,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":6044,"timeElapsed":268147},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678924945,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":5178,"timeElapsed":273327},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678928165,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":3219,"timeElapsed":276547},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678931691,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":3524,"timeElapsed":280073},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678935191,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":3498,"timeElapsed":283573},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678942934,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":6333,"timeElapsed":291316},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678945761,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":2824,"timeElapsed":294142},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678948814,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":3052,"timeElapsed":297196},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678951552,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":2736,"timeElapsed":299934},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678954352,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":2799,"timeElapsed":302734},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678956540,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":2187,"timeElapsed":304922},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678963741,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7199,"timeElapsed":312123},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678967862,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":4119,"timeElapsed":316244},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678971328,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":3464,"timeElapsed":319710},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678974714,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":3384,"timeElapsed":323096},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678979482,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3602,"timeElapsed":327864},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678981852,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":2368,"timeElapsed":330234},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678985091,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":3238,"timeElapsed":333473},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678988267,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":3175,"timeElapsed":336649},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678994813,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":6543,"timeElapsed":343195},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678998076,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":3262,"timeElapsed":346458},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679000963,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":2885,"timeElapsed":349345},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679004850,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":3883,"timeElapsed":353232},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679008435,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":3582,"timeElapsed":356817},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679013852,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5415,"timeElapsed":362234},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679022260,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":6569,"timeElapsed":370642},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679026110,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3848,"timeElapsed":374492},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679030704,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":4592,"timeElapsed":379086},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679032944,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2238,"timeElapsed":381326},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679036750,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3804,"timeElapsed":385132},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679040696,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3944,"timeElapsed":389078},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679044896,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":4198,"timeElapsed":393278},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679049866,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":4968,"timeElapsed":398248},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679051949,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":2080,"timeElapsed":400331},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679060173,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6108,"timeElapsed":408555},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679063691,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":3515,"timeElapsed":412072},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679066674,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":2982,"timeElapsed":415056},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679070577,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":3901,"timeElapsed":418959},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679074654,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4076,"timeElapsed":423036},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679078382,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":3725,"timeElapsed":426763},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679081628,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3245,"timeElapsed":430010},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679085644,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":4014,"timeElapsed":434026},{"subjectID":"podm1cl0s9","prolificID":"645906dc264ac9eb66b7f3ec","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4aa16a7086a77eaa6c","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679090737,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":5090,"timeElapsed":439118}]